Hildebrand, George H. Papers /4040
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ithaca College, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Goulds Pumps vs. USA, Local 3298, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Rochester Telephone vs. Local 1170 CWA, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- GAF Corp. vs. ICW Local 306, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Inspiration -- D. Strickland Case, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Ward La France vs. IAM Local 2562, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- General Dynamic vs. Boilermakers Lodge 614, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- General Dynamics vs. IBEW, Local 261 (May 11-12, 1977) (Box 15, Folder 16)
- U.E. Local 506, Erie PA vs. GE, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Dollinger Corp. vs. IUE Local 329, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Inspiration Consolidated Copper, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Rome City School Dist., 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Wyson Co. vs. RWDSU Local 1195, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- P.D. (El Paso) U.S. of Amer. Dist. 37, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- G.T.E. Sylvania, Inc. - vs. USWA Local 4276, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- GAF Corp. vs. IAMAW Local 1807, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- General Products + International Chem Workers, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- UV Industries - Ruben Silva, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- GAF Corp. vs. ICWU Local 306, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Phelps Dodge vs, UTU Local 1668, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- vs. IAMAW Lodge 1691, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- International Paper Co. vs. UPIU, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Trans World Airlines, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Carborundum, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Union Carbide, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Phelps Dodge - tyrone - Oct. 14.15, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Exhibits - Mine - Mill General Grievance, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Hicks vs. Reynolds Metals, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Louse Purchase, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Southwestern Bell - Houston, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Pollio vs. Teamsters Local 529 Sept. 9, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Phelps Dodge Tyrone Aug. 18, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Shenendehowa Teachers Association vs. Shenendehowa Central School District, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Westinghouse, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Cali Spray-Chemical, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Minneapolis, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- NBC, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- IAM, Lodge 94 and Pabst Brewing Co. Decided Feb. 15 1960 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Inspiration Consolidated Copper Company, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation Douglas Reduction Works, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1947-1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Code of Safe Practice for Roaster Plant Operations, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Code of Safe Practice, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Code of Safe Practice, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Mining Code of the State of Arizona, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Code of Safe Practice for Heavy Truck Drivers, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Phelps Dodge, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers vs. Riverside Cement Co., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- IBEW vs. Salt River Project Decided March 14, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, Local 1-547, and Standard Oil Co. of Calif., El Segundo, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Magma Copper Co. vs. USW 938, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- IUMMSW, Local 568 - Inspiration Copper Co., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Hearts Pub Co. and Los Angeles Mailers No. 9, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- UTWA, Local 76 vs. Hyuck Felt Co., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Inspiration, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Columbia Rope Co. vs. Textile Workers 1085, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Inspiration Copper Vs. Local 586 USW, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Curtiss-Wright vs. USSW, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- General Cable Corp. vs. International Assn. Mach., 1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- GE and UAW Local 191, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- IUE AFL CIO Local 286 and GE, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Abex vs. USS Workers, Local 3145, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Arbitration - El Paso, Miami, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Kennecott - Utah Copper Div., 1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- R.I. Pub. Employees v. Warwick R.H. School, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- US Workers vs. Scott and Wms., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Rca vs. IERandMW, Local 103, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- BLFE and Magma - San Manuel, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- UMWA Local 13886 vs. American smelting and Refining, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- American Bosch Arms Corps. -and- IUE 418, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Acme Electric Company, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Morse Chain vs. IAM and Aerospace Workers, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- ASandR-Mission and Local 310, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Buffalo Bolt Co. and IAM, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Magma vs. IAM Local 2181, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- USS Local No. 5761 vs. Shattuck Denn, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- J.H. Williams US Steelworkers, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Spaulding Fibre Co. Inc., 1961 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Newark Teachers, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- Curtiss-Wright vs. Office, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Sylvania Elec. Vs. IUE, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
- USS, Local 1753 vs. Fedders Corp., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Steelworkers, Loc. 3126 vs. Farrel-Birming., 1962 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- US Metals Refining Co., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Dist. 50. UMWA vs. Spec. Chem., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- Ward Baking Company, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- UMW Dist. 50 Local 12330 Nat'l Aniline (Allied Chem), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 37)
- NASBET vs. WHEC. Inc., 1961 (Box 19, Folder 38)
- Nat'l Assoc. of Broadcast Emp. G Tech. vs. Capital Cities Broadcasting Corp., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 39)
- United Steelworkers, Loc. 3937; Reynolds, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Phelps Dodge Corp., el Paso, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 41)
- Reynolds Metals at Massena, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 42)
- PD - Decisions and Opinions, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 43)
- Local 616 IUMMSW vs. PD, Morenci, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 44)
- AAA Decision Forms (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Shell Oil, Dominguez -and- OCAWIU, Local 1-128, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Arbitration: International Association of Machinists Aeronautical, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Hillsboro Newspaper Printing Company Division of Hearst Publishing Company -and- Los Angeles Mailers Union No. 9 International Typographical Union, 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Librascope Incorporated -and- Precision Lodge No. 1600, IAM, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Bekins Van and Storage Company vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Van and Storage Drivers, Packers, Warehousemen and Helpers Local Union 389, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- NBC, Inc. -and- National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Union Local No. 400 -and- Food Employers Council, Inc., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Zenith Meat Company -and- Butchers Union, Local No. 653, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union AFL-CIO, Local 1-128 vs. Union Oil Company of California, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Kennecott Copper Corp. (Ray Mines Division) and United Steelworkers, Local 5252, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- International Association of Machinists Aeronautical Industrial Local Lodge 2207 -and- Lockheed Aircraft Service, Inc. Special Devices Division Pomona, Calif., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Kennecott Copper Corporation Chino Mines Division -and- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Local 890, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Reynolds Metals Co. (Phoenix Aviola Parts Plant) -and- United Steelworkers Local 3937, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- United Steelworkers of America Local Union No. 2018 -and- southwest Steel Rolling Mills, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union AFL-CIO Santa Maria Local no. 1-534 Union Oil Company of California, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Technicolor corporation -and- Film Technicians, Local 683 IATSE and MPMO, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Federal Envelope Co., Los Angeles Plant vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union No. 388, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles Typographical Union Local 174 -and- Service Typographers, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- U.S. Steel Supply Division L.A. District Warehouse -and- United Steelworkers, Local 1981, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Arbitration: Standard Products Co. (West Coast Division) and United Steelworkers of Amer. AFL-CIO, Local 1981, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- United Steelworkers of America Local 3937 Phoenix, Arizona, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Arbitration: Reynolds Metals Company and United Steelworkers of America, Aluminum Division, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Utah Mining (San Manual), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- United Steelworkers, Phoenix Local 3937, and Reynolds Metals Company Decided January 30, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- UN. Steelworkers., Alum. Division., Local 3937 -and- Reynolds Metals, Phoenix, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Reynolds Metals v. USA - 7 cases September 1955 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- United Steelworkers, Local 3937 v. Reynolds Metals, Phoenix Cases for January-May 1954 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- American Can Company, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- American Can Company, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- American Can Company, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh Printing Pressmen's Union Local No. 9, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Printing Pressmen's Union No. 9, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Magma Copper Company, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Aeronaut. Ind. District Lodge 727, IAM vs. Lockheed Aircraft Corp., Calif.. Division, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Ind. Union of Petroleum Workers, and Standard Oil Co. of Calif. 10/12/54, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Southern California Gas Company vs. Utility Workers UN. Of Am., Local 132, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- OWIU vs. Union Oil Co., La Rfry., 1954 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Menasco Co. v. IAM Local 758, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers vs. Grunwald-Marx Company, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers - Local 1-128 -and- fletcher Oil Company, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Gladding, McBean and Co., and United Brick and Clay Workers, AFL, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Rheem Manufacturing Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 4670, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Arbitration: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 274 and The Borden Company (Phoenix), 1959 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Arbitration: International Assoc. of Machinists and Lockheed Aircraft Corp. (New Mexico), 1959 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Arbitration: Monogram Precision Industries, Inc. and International Assoc. of Machinists, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- San Manuel Copper Corporation -and- Mine, Mill Local 937, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Metropolitan coach Lines -and- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Utah Construction (Pima), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- International Association of Machinists, Aeronautical Industrial Local Lodge 821 -and- Lockheed Aircraft Service, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America -and- Armco Drainage and Metal Products, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Emerson-Pryne Company -and- IBEW, Local 1710, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Arbitration: San Manuel Copper Corp. (Tucson) -and- International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Shell Chemical, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- United Rubber Cork Linoleum, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Arbitration: Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union; Local 37 and Dolly Madison Baking Co., 1959 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Arbitration: Aerojet-General Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 1893, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Arbitration: International Chemical Workers, Local 1 and Mastic tils Corporation, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Arbitration: Pomona Tile Company and Organizing Committee for Ceramic Tile Workers Local no. 923, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Arbitration: National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, AFL-CIO-CLS and National Broadcasting Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- International Chemical Workers Union #52 -and- Lever Brothers company, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- International Chemical Workers Union, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Bakery and Confectionery Workers' Local Union, No. 37, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International -and- General Petroleum Corp., 1958 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Arbitration: The American Brass Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 5726, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Pacific Press vs. Los Angeles Mailers 9 Decided March 30, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- International Chemical Workers, Local 452 vs. Lever Brothers Company, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Lockheed Aircraft Corporation vs. Aeronautical District Lodge 727, IAM Dec. 8, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Brungswig Drug v. ILWU, Local 26 San Diego, Feb. 29, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- LA Transit Lines v. Transp. Union 1277 September, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Kay Manufacturing Corporation v. Wood Workers Union--Local 576, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Axelson Mfg. v. IAM, Lodge 94 September, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- ASandR, Fed. Metals Division., and IUMMSW Local 700, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Librascope Incorporated v. IAM, Precision Lodge No. 1600 July 1, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Douglas Aircraft, El Segumbo v. District Lodge 720, IAM Nov. 28, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Superior Sleeprite Corporation v. Furn. Workers., Upholstery and wood Workers, 576, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Off. Wkrs. Int. Union, Loc. No. 174 v. RKP Radio Pictures Corp. 11/54, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Food MCHY and Chem. Corp., Mech. Fdries. Div. v. Intl. Molders and Fdry Wkrs, 374, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Day and Night, Payne Furnace Division., Carriers Corp. v. Teamsters 196 July, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 30)